So y'all are really just, in my comments, just really going ham, like, you're voting for Trump.
And I'm just like, do y'all understand what primaries are?
But the same people are frustrated with the government.
The same people are frustrated with the way Joe Biden governs.
So I'm just like, I just want y'all to understand that there are levers that you can pull.
There are things that you can do to show a candidate, like, hey, you better do more.
And it's lost on me that you all don't even think that there's something valuable in making him think, yeah, I might vote for this other person.
So you need to give me what I want.
Why do y'all think that we don't have a right to do that?
Like, it's just, think, like, if you get to the finish of your thought, I want you to then, when you get to the finish line of your thought, I want you to ask yourself, can I go further?
And then venture further.
Venture further into the trees that you've never stepped through.
Consider a different way of thinking than what you've been told to do.
Especially do that before you come in my comments trying to act like I don't know what I'm talking about.
When y'all be following me every flippin' day because I know what I'm talking about.
You think all of a sudden today I just don't know what the hell I'm doing?
Come on.
Give yourselves more credit than that.